A Guide to the W.E. Bibb Papers
University of Virginia Library
- SERIES V: BOUND VOLUMES & OVERSIZE MATERIAL
  - SUBSERIES A: BOXED BOUND VOLUMES
    - Mineral City Mining, Manufacturing & Land Company: Stock Sales Record., 1890-1892 (Box Box 42.)
    - [Thomas Family ?]: Sawmill Account Books., ca 1899-1905; (2 Volumes). (Box Box 42.)
    - W. Worth Smith: Law Office Ledger., 1915-1922 (Box Box 42.)
    - World War I Scrapbook with notes on the history of English Law., 1918 June (Box Box 42.)
    - Ledgers with indexes., 1907-1914; (2 volumes). (Box Box 43.)
    - Smith, Boyd: Miscellaneous Checkstubs., 1893-1903; (29 bound items). (Box Box 43.)
    - Political Scrapbook with newsclippings & comments., 1876 (Box Box 44.)
    - Check Stubs: Miscellaneous., 1896-1917 (Box Box 44.)
    - Bibb, W.E.: Bank Books., 1884-1899; (7 items) (Box Box 44.)
      For additional Bibb bound volumes see boxes 34-37.
  - SUBSERIES B: 2M BOUND VOLUMES
    - Louisa County Tax Book, 1866-1867
    - Mineral City Mining, Manufacturing, & Land Company: Checks, 1891-1892
    - Mineral City Mining, Manufacturing, & Land Company: Journal, 1890-1892
    - Mineral City Mining, Manufacturing, & Land Company: Ledger with index, 1890-1891
    - Mineral City Mining, Manufacturing, & Land Company: Stock Certificate Book, 1890-1893
    - Mineral City Mining, Manufacturing, & Land Company: Stock Register, 1890-1892
  - SUBSERIES C: OVERSIZE FOLDERS
    - M-19
      - Broadside "Commissioner's Sale of Louisa Land," listing H.W. Murray, W.B. Pettit, and W.E. Bibb as Special Commissioners, 1874 Nov 9
      - Broadside "Commissioner's Sale of Louisa Land," listing H.W. Murray, W.B. Pettit, and W.E. Bibb as Special Commissioners, 1875 May 10
      - Broadside "Commissioner's Sale of Land in Louisa," listing H.W. Murray and W.E. Bibb as Special Commissioners (2 copies), 1875 Aug 9
      - Copy of a Survey of Reuben B. Davis Estate at Tolersville, Virginia, surveyed by T.B. Madison, 1881 May
      - Plat of land lying Louisa County sold by Benjamin S. Francisco, Trustee, to Marshal Winston, surveyed by Everett Perkins, 1881 Sep 7
      - Broadside "Louisa Lands For Sale," listing W.E. Bibb as Special Commissioner, 1886 Nov 8
      - The Hamburg-Bremen Fire Insurance Company Policy for a residence on Campbell Street, Roanoke, Virginia, purchased by W.E. Bibb from [D.C. Moomaw], 1888 Apr 9
      - Broadside "Valuable Real Estate at Mineral City, VA. For Sale," J.G. May, Trustee (3 copies), 1898 Jul 5
      - Broadside "Louisa Land For Sale! 192 Valuable Mineral City Lots!," W.E. Bibb, Special Commissioner (3 copies), 1898 Dec 10
      - List of the names of all persons who have paid their capitation tax on or before May 4, 1907, in Mineral Magisterial District, Louisa Court-House District, Green Spring District, and an unidentified District, with separate lists for white and black men (4 items), 1907 May 4
      - Plats of the Poindexter tract, within and along the Elizabeth River, (2 items)
      - Printed map of the property of The Dominion Mining & Chemical Company, Louisa County, Virginia, surveyed by W.L. Bishop, n.d.
      - Printed Map of the cities of Norfolk and Portsmouth and Vicinity (2 copies)
      - Prospectus for the Greenbrier White Sulphur Springs Company, n.d.
  - OVERSIZE TRAY 34
    - Norfolk & Western Railroad and Connections Printed Map, 1889 Jul; 32 X 33 inches
    - Printed plan of lots for sale in Mineral City, Louisa County, Virginia drawn by W.L. Bishop, 1890; ca. 34 X 46 inches
    - Printed Map showing the Lands of the Columbialand Company of Roanoke City, Virginia, north of the Roanoke River, prepared by G. William Baist of Philadelphia, 1891 Feb; ca. 22 X 31 inches
    - Advertising Poster for Raymold's Reliable Regalia, New York City, featuring various regalia, paraphernalia, and jewels for secret fraternal orders, 28 X 40 inches